gadgetsandgear.com 2011-06-01

# 

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

 _This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the  [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo

**Our Privacy& Security Statement**

Unfortunately, we live in a very litigious society. GadgetsandGear.com has developed the following policies to protect us and our valued customers from fraudulent transactions.  

At GadgetsandGear.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a better shopping experience. We've partnered with world leaders in technology and security to provide you with an easy to use, fully secure on-line shopping experience.  **We will NEVER sell, rent or give your personal information away.**

**Collecting Information**

When you order from GadgetsandGear.com, we ask for specific information so that we can fulfill your order, send you messages regarding your order by e-mail and further enhance your shopping experience. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. The information collected will be kept confidential and used to support your transaction with BrickHouse Electronics. This site uses an order form to process all transactions.

Here is a list of the information we collect at GadgetsandGear.com, as well as how we use it:  

  1. When you place an order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, shipping address, billing address, phone number, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order, as well as notify you of your order status.

  2. Financial information that's collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

  3. At GadgetsandGear.com, we're always striving to improve your shopping experience by personalizing it. We constantly monitor customer traffic patterns in an effort to help us improve the site's functionality.

**Security (Protecting Customer Information)**

This site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

We use state-of-the-art technology to protect and secure your transactional information from unauthorized third parties. GadgetsandGear.com uses industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name and address as it is transmitted over the Internet. Our secure server is also protected by firewall technology to prevent unauthorized access to any information that we store.  

GadgetsandGear.com guarantees secure transactions; protecting our customers' information is of utmost concern to us. Every employee servicing GadgetsandGear.com is made aware of and is expected to comply with all of our Privacy & Security Policies. **  
**

**Disclosing Information**

GadgetsandGear.com respects your privacy. GadgetsandGear.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information. GadgetsandGear.com may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of GadgetsandGear.com, our users or others. **  
**

**Credit Card Fraud Protection**

GadgetsandGear.com employs various Credit Card Fraud Prevention Services, provided by our Online Merchant Processor, in order to insure purchases made from GadgetsandGear.com are not fraudulent. When you transmit credit card information to complete a purchase or verify data, we always transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format (SSL) to prevent unauthorized transactions. Federal Law states that your credit card provider cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of any fraudulent charge. In the event of an unauthorized use of your credit card, you must report this problem immediately to your credit card provider in accordance with its terms of use.
